{
    "subject": "resource/Andrea_Ferro",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Singing",
    "human_readable": "The instrument of Andrea Ferro is singing.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9264808893203735,
            "question": "Is Andrea Ferro a singer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677219152450562,
            "question": "What instrument does Andrea Ferro play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8035497665405273,
            "question": "In what genre does Andrea Ferro perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7983725070953369,
            "question": "Does Andrea Ferro use any other instruments besides singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6831753253936768,
            "question": "Are there any other notable musicians who play similar instruments to Andrea Ferro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6568688750267029,
            "question": "What kind of music does Andrea Ferro create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6231966018676758,
            "question": "What is Andrea Ferro known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251865386962891,
            "question": "Where is Andrea Ferro from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4822986125946045,
            "question": "What are some of Andrea Ferro's most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.396991491317749,
            "question": "Has Andrea Ferro ever collaborated with other artists?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The instrument of Andrea Ferro is singing.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1363_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Andrea Ferro's most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1363_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Andrea Ferro from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1363_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Andrea Ferro known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1363_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1363_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Andrea Ferro, including her role as a vocalist for the band Lacuna Coil. This supports the statement that the instrument of Andrea Ferro is singing."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}